我叫Max 我是你们的服务员
I'm Max. I'll be your waitress,
因为他们在这里不做背景调查
'cause they don't do background checks here.
我知道你是我们的服务员
Oh, you'll be our waitress.
我绝不是根据制服进行猜测的
I never guessed that based on the uniform
也不是因为你的名牌上写了"Max"
and name tag that says "Max."
你知道我能赚个三美元吗?
You know I make, like, $3, right?
这在九十世纪二十年代可是一笔巨款了
I realize that's a lot of money in the 1920s
就是你们处于的那个时代
where you two are from.
把这酒打开 给我们拿两个干净的玻璃杯
Here, open this and bring us two clean glasses.
当然可以 不伟大的盖茨比
Sure, Not-So-Great Gatsby.
嘿 杀人犯及前妻
Hey, OJ and Nicole.
十号桌有几个粗鲁的势利鬼 你懂的
Rude snobs at table ten. You know what that means.
- 把酒掉包?  - 来吧
- Wine swap?  - Let's roll.
嘿 Oleg 我要一瓶那种从你表兄脖子
Hey, Oleg, I need one of those $2 Merlots
插孔搞出来的 两块钱一瓶的梅洛红酒
you get from your cousin with the hole in his neck.
Caroline 查一下这个多少钱
Caroline, price check.
哇! 这是柏菲酒庄2008年产的 很贵啊
Oh! Chateau Pavie, 2008. Very expensive.
不过 这是我们应得的
But, hey, we deserve it.
给你 最好给它透透气
Here, better let it breathe.
之前它被放在我的运动包里了
It was in my gym bag.
没问题
Not a problem.
这对复古夫妻喜欢护身三角绷带
This vintage pairs well with jockstrap.
你认为在我有钱的时候 服务员也是这样对我的吗
Do you think waitresses did this to me when I had money?
如果你态度不好就会
Only if you had an attitude.
看来答案是会了
So that's a yes.
我都有点记不清了
I can't remember if this reminds me
这让我想起自己在参与打劫时
of an old heist movie I saw on an old heist
看到的一个关于打劫的电影
I actually participated in.
我们像是便利店版的11罗汉
I know. We're like Ocean's 7/11.
现在我们就缺一个小个子的
All we're missing is a tiny asian guy
可以装进小箱子的亚洲男人
who can fit into small boxes.
你们好
Hello.
十号桌在等着上酒呢
Table ten is looking for their wine.
没问题 这就来
Oh, not a problem. Coming right up.
你们干什么了? 她在笑什么?
What did you do? Why is she smiling?
我的裤子又着火了吗?
Are my pants on fire again?
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫
时间轴: 。沫
翻译: Astral  波特妹子  morning  Navy Seal
校对: 桃茜茜
受死吧 臭老鼠!
Oh, yeah, take that, sucker!
Max 当我说
Max, when I said
我们得把纸杯蛋糕拿开
we need to move the cupcakes,
我是叫你别把蛋糕扔到啮齿目动物的头上
I didn't mean through the air at a rodent's head.
嘿 它刚刚跑到窗户上去了
Hey, he ran up the window,
所以现在是坚守阵地的问题了
so it's kind of a stand-your-ground situation.
好了 我们暂停一会 他在吃我的弹药
Okay, we're on a time-out. He's eating my ammo.
Max 生意又下滑了
Max, business is down again,
而我说的比这话还多的就是
and the only phrase I've said more than that is,
"神啊 让我在睡梦中死去吧"
"Please, god, take me in my sleep."
很显然 没什么进展啊
I mean, it's clear. Not getting ahead.
噢 你心情不好就是因为这个?
Oh, is that what your mood is about?
因为没有人进你?
You're not getting any ahead?
因为我只要一通电话就能帮你解决
'cause I can take care of that with one call.
你不能把我介绍给那个在你手机里
You are not hooking me up with that guy
标注着"口交巴克"的家伙
who's listed in your phone as "oral redenbacher."
Max 这是我们的未来
Max, this is our future.
我们得认真赚钱
We need to get serious about making money.
当然 我们早点走吧
Absolutely. Let's leave early.
早退? 你当我们是谁啊 国会?
Leave early? Who are we, Congress?
你以为其他人做生意是
Do you think other business got successful
靠早退成功的吗?
by leaving early?
当然不 他们成功是因为他们
No, they did it by hiring illegals
雇佣了非法移民 并把财产转移到海外
and moving their bank accounts offshore.
我们不能早退
We can't leave early.
这标牌上写着"营业时间到凌晨两点"
The sign says "open till 2:00 a.m."
好吧 我打算换张新牌子 上面写着"关门"
Well, I'm open to getting a new sign that says "closed."
我是说 难道我们就应该呆在这里
I mean, are we supposed to just hang around here
等哪个闲逛的神经病来我们店吗?
and wait for whatever nut jobs are trolling around town?
大家好
Hi, girls.
你们猜我和Oleg打算做件什么
Guess what Oleg and I are going to do
可能会让我得丙肝的事吗
that will probably give me hep c.
和汤米・李玩三人行?
A three way with Tommy Lee?
别傻了 我们是要去纹个情侣纹身
No, silly. We're getting matching tattoos.
我们想要个可以代表我们关系的图样
We want something that represents our relationship.
可以纹两只在"犯罪现场调查: 迈阿密"中
So maybe two butterflies doing the nasty
嘿咻的蝴蝶
during "CSI: Miami."
哇 你们两个真不错 一对纹身
Wow, you two, his and her tats.
很浪漫 还能有助于辨别尸体
Romantic and will help identify the bodies.
当然 情侣纹身
Sure, you know, matching tattoos
最能表达承诺的方式
are the deepest expression of commitment.
对的 情侣纹身
Well, matching tattoos
以及在对方面前拉屎
and pooping in front of each other.
我可不会在我男人面前拉屎
I'm not gonna do it in front of my man.
我在麦当劳拉屎 因为我是个淑女
I poop at McDonald's 'cause I'm a lady.
谢谢你们的纸杯蛋糕
Thanks for the cupcake.
我们真应该算她的账
We really have to start charging her.
算她啥账啊 一级搞定男人罪?
Charge her with what, first-degree man-settling?
Max 我之前也说了 我们该
Max, as I was saying, it's time to get serious
认真对待这个生意了
about the business.
当然 我们提早离开吧
Absolutely. Let's leave early.
怎么了? 昨晚一点钟过后
What? Last night after 1:00,
我们只赚了15美元 对吧?
we made only $15, right?
其实是14.63美元
$14.63.
怎么 我很拿手数学啊
What? Math is my thing.
如果你看到艾米纳姆在你对面开始说唱
Would you roll your eyes if you were standing
你还会翻白眼吗
across from Eminem and he started rapping?
当然
Uh, yes.
我会说"老兄 你都六十岁了 洗洗睡吧"
I'd be all, "Dude, you're 60. Sit on a porch swing."
好吧 你看 这里有15美元
Okay, look, here is $15.
差不多就是我们能赚的钱了
That'll cover what we'll probably make.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
你就打算把我抛在这里?
You're just gonna leave me here?
是的 等你把那14.63美元的差价找给我
Yup, I'm leaving as soon as I get my change back
我就马上走
from that $14.63.
好啊 告诉我我该找你多少钱
Fine, just tell me how much that is.
我还是早点走吧
Or maybe sooner.
这是个很重要的日子
This is a very big day for me.
为什么? 因为这个商业研讨会
Why, because of this totally out-of-the-blue order
给咱们来了个突如其来的蛋糕订单?
we got to do cupcakes for this business seminar?
当然不是 今天是我第一次从大门
No, the first time I've entered a Sheridan
走进喜来登酒店
through a door.
我通常都是翻窗或者走货运电梯的
Usually it's by window or freight elevator.
还有一次 我躲在一个女孩的
And one time, I rolled in under some girl's
裙子下钻进来的
Quinceara dress.
研讨会马上就要开始了
The seminar's about to start.
这里仍有几个名牌没人拿的 Pamela和Ellen...
I have unclaimed name tags for Pamela, Ellen...
有什么烂人会来这种地方?
What kind of losers would come to this?
还有Max和Caroline
Max, Caroline.
我可不会称我们为烂人
I wouldn't call us losers.
你们来了吗?
Are you here?
好吧 其实没有人订纸杯蛋糕
Okay, so there is no cupcake order.
我给咱们报名参加这研讨会
I signed us up for this seminar.
我白白拿着这么多纸杯蛋糕挤了一路地铁?
I carried cupcakes on a subway for nothing?
坐我旁边的唠叨女人可是说了一路啊
The annoying woman next to me talked the whole time.
Max 坐你旁边的人是我
I was sitting next to you, Max.
我知道你是怎么都不肯来的
Look, I knew you wouldn't come otherwise,
而且你确实需要来这一趟
and you need to be here.
你这叫商业干预
This is a business intervention.
这不是干预
It's not an intervention.
Man 你最近的表现在以下几个
Max, your behavior lately has affected me
方面影响到了我
in the following ways.
有没有搞错
I can't believe this.
最起码其他的劝诫会上我是醉着的
At least in my other interventions I was drunk.
我们需要这次讲座
We need to do this seminar.
Gordon Kepper是个天才
Gordon Kepper is a genius.
他会让我们的生意达到高潮的
He's gonna give our business a real bump.
我第二次劝诫会就是因为
Guys giving me a bump is why they threw me
那些给我高潮的家伙
that second intervention.
我们走吧
Let's go.
好吧 你不走我走
Oh, mm, okay. See you.
这就是你的新爱好吗 Max?
So this is your new thing, Max?
你就这么扔下我不管了?
You're just gonna walk out on me?
实际上 这是老习惯了
Actually, it's an old thing.
其实 这算是家庭传统了
In fact, it's kind of a family tradition.
我从我爸那里学来的 虽然不知道他是谁
I learned from my father, whoever he is.
拜托 就两天而已
Come on. It's just two days.
两天? 没门
Two days? No way.
绝对不可能
No freaking way.
这里有自助餐和甜点吧
There's a buffet and a dessert bar.
没问题
Ooh, okay.
等一下 我去交钱 我带了点现金
Wait here, I'll go pay. I brought some cash.
过期的超市礼品卡也能用的 对吧?
And they'll take an expired Target gift card, right?
我们才不交钱
Oh, we are not paying.
这里 给你 Pamela
Here. Here, Pamela.
跟着Ellen去货运电梯吧
Follow Ellen to the freight elevator.
不行 Max 我们不能溜进去
No way, Max. We are not sneaking in.
- 这玩意儿多少钱?  - 一千刀
- How much is this thing?  - $1,000.
我们得溜进去 Ellen
We're sneaking in, Ellen.
各位 你们今天在此
Now, you all are here today
不只是要找到自己在商业中的定位
not only to find out what you are as a business
还要找到人生方向
but to find out who you are.
我的人生目标就是希望自助餐
I'm a lady hoping there's macaroni and cheese
有通心粉和奶酪
at that buffet.
你自己就是品牌
Who are you is your brand,
说品牌不过是个名字
and saying that a brand is simply a name
就好像说亚伯拉罕・林肯不过就是代号而已
is like saying Abraham Lincoln is simply a name,
还有圣雄甘地 上帝
or Mahatma Gandhi, God.
这家伙以为自己是谁啊?
Who does this guy think he is?
你肯定正在想 "这家伙以为自己是谁啊?"
I'm sure you're wondering, "who does this guy think he is?"
好吧 这也太诡异了
Okay, that was weird.
或者是想着这挺诡异的
Or maybe this seems weird.
我起鸡皮疙瘩了
I've got chills.
一谈到生意
When it comes to business,
大家总是来找我
people come up to me all the time.
他们说 "Gordon 做生意太难了
They say, "Gordon, business is hard,
但我已经尽力了"
but I do what I can."
然后他们耸耸肩 请问 这是正确的态度吗?
And they shrug. Now, is that the right attitude?
- 不是  - 是
- No.  - Yes.
对这些人 我说 "不要只是尽力
To those people, I say, "don't do what you can.
要竭尽全力"
Can what you do."
不要只是尽力
Don't do what you can.
要竭尽全力! 懂了吗?
Can what you do! Get it?
懂了吗?
Do you get it?
- 是  - 没有
- Yes.  - No.
- 你根本没懂  - 嘘
- You did not get it.  - Shh.
好了 各位 把手伸到座位下面
All right, everybody, reach under your chairs
看看找到了什么
and pick up what you find there.
希望是出去的方法
Hope it's a way out of here.
毛毛球?
Koosh balls?
在这些罐子里 你能找到
Inside those cans, you will find the key
商业成功的方法
to success in your business.
如果所谓的方法就是罗茜・奥唐纳
Not unless the key is Rosie O'Donnell's career
剪西瓜头前的样子
before her buzz cut.
真诚
Truth.
这就是生意的秘诀
That's the big secret to business.
如果人们相信你的话
If people buy what you're saying,
他们就会去买你的货
they will buy what you're selling.
Max 好好听 这分分钟变成商业圣会
Max, stay alert. This could go to cult like that.
我喜欢把你们手中拿着的东西
I like to think of those things you're holding
视为我的真理球
as my truth balls.
得了吧 不如直接说是肉丸
Screw this. Let's get to the meatballs.
在接下来的两天里
Anytime in the next two days,
你们中随时有人会上台来推销
one of you is up here selling you something
你觉得是胡说八道的东西
that you feel is just bull,
那就扔出去...
Then toss it...
Max啊!
Max!
我是说 Ellen!
I mean, Ellen!
没错 亲
Yeah, baby.
我说的就是这样
That is what I'm talking about.
扔球的人是个不畏艰险
Whoever threw that is not afraid
勇往直前的人
to really go for it,
这会助她在成功路上
And that will go a long way
走很远的
toward success in business.
好吧 但是去自助的路远吗?
All right, cool, but it is a long way to the buffet?
因为老娘都快饿死了
'Cause I am starving.
好了 各位
Okay, everyone.
把这些你们分成的小组
consider these small groups you've broken into
视为小的智囊团们
as little think tanks.
我希望你们齐心协力想出最好的点子
I need you to work together and bring out your very best.
Max啊!
Max!
别怪我
Don't blame me.
要怪意大利宽面上的奶油太多
Blame the heavy cream at the fettuccini bar.
意大利人肯定把芝士当"安眠药"了
Alfredo must be Italian for "roofie."
那么 Ellen 告诉我们你会什么
So, Ellen, tell us what you have,
我就告诉你我们的想法
and I'll tell you what we think.
哦 Ellen 说你呢
Oh, Ellen. That's you.
哦哦 对 是我
Oh, oh, yes, yes, that's me.
我是Ellen 如假包换的Ellen
I'm Ellen. Definitely an Ellen.
看到没 我会跳舞
See, I dance.
很好
Okay.
好吧 这下真的好尴尬
Okay. Okay, now it's weird.
那么 Ellen...
So, Ellen...
让我们听听你的BBB论...
Let's hear your B.B.B....
你才智卓绝的生意品牌
Your brilliant business brand.
呃...
Uh...
我... 我平常不说话 Pamela负责发言
I... I don't do the talking. Pamela does the talking.
- Pam?  - 谢谢 Ellen
- Pam?  - Thanks, Ellen.
大家好 我叫Pam Panning
Hello, everyone, my name is Pam Panning,
我的生意伙伴 Ellen 想说的是
And what my partner, Ellen, was trying to say is,
我们做的杯糕工艺精湛
we making very beautiful artisan cupcakes.
没错 但同时很酷
Yeah, but they're still cool.
我也没说它们不酷啊
I never said they weren't cool.
哼 或许因为从你嘴里说出来
Yeah, mm, maybe they just didn't sound cool
就显得不酷了
coming out of your face.
不好意思 至少能说出话
I'm sorry, but at least actual words
好过你的"呃呃呃..."
Are better than, "uh, uh-uh, uh..."
女士们 暂停一下
Ladies, hold.
有时在生意上
Sometimes in business
合作伙伴就像是两艘驶向不同方向的船
partner' ships will sail in two different directions,
这时你们需要明确 你们是
so you two need to find out if you're gonna continue
分道扬镳 还是转变航线
to sail apart or if you're gonna change course
重新达成共识
and reconvene at the port of mutual understanding.
我俩没法分得太开
Well, we can't sail too far apart
因为我肯定还得跟她解释
'cause I'm definitely gonna have to explain
你刚刚说的话
what you just said to her.
我听懂了
I got it.
我是艘船 而且我想要离你远点
I'm a boat, and I'm trying to get away from you.
说得太对了
Sounds right to me.
好好想想
Think it over.
跟你的大副商量一下
Talk it over with your first mate.
明天回来
Come back tomorrow
告诉我你们的生意是什么
and tell me who your business is,
我会指导你们朝着目标前进
and I'll help guide you toward that purpose.
记住 你要想爆发 就得...
And remember, you can't purpose without...
- 找个阴道 - 好了 够了
- Puss.  - Okay, wow.
Gordon 她的船现在像是进入浅水区了
Gordon, her boat's kind of in shallow water right now,
但我们准备回去 达成共识
but we're gonna go away, get it together,
再回来让你大吃一惊
and come back and blow you away.
"大吃一惊"需要...
And you can't spell "blow you away" without...
我们的船要开走了
Our ship's leaving.
哦 你们好
Oh, hello.
欢迎来到威廉斯堡小餐厅
Welcome to the Williamsburg diner.
请问需要来点什么 比如说职业道德?
Can I get you anything, like a work ethic?
Han 你真是太可爱了 但我们忙着呢
Han, this is adorable, but we're busy.
我们正在定位我们的商业品牌
We're pitching our business brand tomorrow,
我和Max需要达成共识
and Max and I need to get on the same page.
没错 我们不想下半辈子
Yeah, we don't want to work here
还在这里干活
the rest of our lives.
现在我们达成共识了
Well, now we're all on the same page.
Han 给我们十分钟就好
Han, just give us ten minutes.
然后我们就回去工作
Then we'll get to work.
好吧 我都等了四年了
Well, I've waited four years.
再等十分钟又怎样?
What's another ten minutes?
Max 我不得不说我被你
Max, I have to say I was a little thrown
今天说的话给吓到了
by that thing you said today.
哪句 我说我最棒的性体验是
What, that the best sex I've ever had
自己独自坐大摆锤的时候?
was alone on the tilt-a-whirl?
不 这怎么吓得了我 你每天都这么说的
No, why would that throw me? You say that every day.
不 是你说我听起来不酷的那话儿
No, that thing about me not sounding cool.
这句怎么吓到你了? 我每天都说这种话
Why would that throw you? I say it every day.
对 但以前说的不是做生意
Yes, but not about the business.
这叫什么来着? "艺工"?
So what was it? The word "artisan"?
首先 它听起来像"屁工"
Okay, first of all, it sounds like fart-isan,
好比"现在这里就有人放了个屁"
As in, "a fart is in this room right now."
终于有人跟你说出这话了 Caroline
Somebody finally called you out on it, Caroline.
所以我想的口号是
So I was thinking our slogan could be,
"Max自制的纸杯蛋糕 又甜又香"
"Max's homemade cupcakes. Sugar and spice."
我宁愿用"屁工"
I'd rather go with fart-isan.
真的吗 瘪四?
Really, beavis?
Beavis and Butt-head:瘪四与大头蛋 重口卡通片
你的合作伙伴大头蛋是怎么想的?
What does your business partner butthead think?
我们的店都没什么活儿
Our business isn't working.
猜猜谁在干活
Well, guess who is working.
是我 餐厅老板
Me, the damn owner.
你惊讶什么?
Why are you surprised?
你知道有多少纸杯蛋糕卖不出去
You know how many cupcakes were not selling.
你一晚上至少偷吃六个蛋糕
I mean, you're secretly eating at least six a night
好让我以为我们卖得更多了
to make me think we're selling more.
也因为我心情不好
Also 'cause I'm sad.
听着 我知道你上过沃顿商学院 但是...
Look, I know you went to Wharton and all, but...
等等..,
Wait...
什么情况?
What's happening?
这是对我的商业干预吗?
Is this a business intervention on me?
从那个把"生意"
From someone who pronounces
读成"伤意"的人嘴里说出?
the word business "bidness"?
你干嘛一副瞪大眼睛的表情?
Why are you giving me the big eye-painting face?
你知道我们的生意不好
You knew the business wasn't working.
但我没听你提过任何想法
Well, I don't hear you coming up with any ideas.
那是因为你从来不听
That's 'cause you don't listen.
我说过我们应该不再做
Remember when I said we should stop making
那种花哨的纸杯蛋糕
all these flowery cupcakes
而是直接写上刻薄的话
and just make ones that say mean things
比如"去死" "舔我"?
like "eat it" and "lick me"?
你宏大的生意计划就是在蛋糕上
Your big business plan is cupcakes
写"去死"和"舔我"?
that say "eat it" and "lick me"?
还有别的 比如说"潘"
And other funny things like "loser"
或者是"回味无穷"
or "eat your feelings."
嗯 那还不如在顾客来到窗边时
Hmm, why not just shoot people in the face
直接射他们一脸呢?
when they come to the window?
我觉得我们的衬衫后面
And I thought the back of our t-shirt
可以写上"奶油爆满"
could just say, "cream filled."
如果如果一个性感妞穿着 会很有趣的
So funny if, like, a hot girl was wearing it.
如果是个胖子穿着就更搞笑了
And even funnier if it was a fat guy.
好吧 也许就像Gordon说的
Okay, maybe like Gordon said,
我们的合作之船 驶向不同的地方了
our partner ships are going in different directions.
我的"又甜又香"号驶向一边
My sugar and spice ship is going one way,
而你的"尖酸刻薄"号
and your mean and ugly booze cruise
驶向了另一边
is going another.
要不明天这样 我开我的船
So how about tomorrow, I'll sail my ship,
你开你的船 Ellen
and you can sail yours, Ellen.
没问题
Done.
对了 Pam 我知道你觉得自己的船不会沉
And, Pam, I know you think your ship don't sink,
但它真的会沉
but it does.
Hannah和Todd 开始吧
So, Hannah, Todd, go.
告诉我们 你们的生意是什么?
Tell us, who is your business?
我们做的是吉他包旅行包
We make guitar case suitcases.
没错 那是外形像吉他包的旅行包
Yeah, they're suitcases that look like guitar cases
这样你就可以在机场装酷
So you can look cool at the airport.
目前为止 没有真理球
So far, no truth balls.
这意味着大家相信你们所描述的生意理念
That means we believe you're telling some truth
是有道理的
of who you are.
做生意总是...
Business is always...
好吧
Okay then.
这有什么 他们的想法
So what, their big idea
不就是把你的杂物都塞进一个吉他包里?
is just throwing your crap in a guitar case?
起码不是"屁工"纸杯蛋糕
Well, it's no fart-isan cupcake.
Todd和Hannah 你们有没有跟我们的艺术家一起
Todd, Hannah, did you get together with our graphic artist
设计一个商标呢?
to help create a logo?
有 我们设计出了
Yes, we did.
我们花了整个通宵 说实话
We stayed up all night, and to be honest,
商标有点奇怪
it got kind of weird.
这就是我们的商标
That's our logo,
我们公司就叫"我和乐队是一伙的"
And our company's called "I'm with the band."
够了!
Back off!
她刚从康复中心出来
She just got out of rehab.
胆小鬼是做不成生意的
Business is not for the faint of heart
瘾君子也不能做生意
or coke addicts.
下一组 我们有请Ellen和Pam
Next up, we've got Ellen and Pam.
给点儿掌声鼓励她们一下
Let's give 'em some love.
Max 你真的不能到上面去
Max, you're really not gonna go up there
把你的想法当做生意卖点
and sell your idea as a business plan.
当然能 而且我的感觉很好
Yup, and I feel pretty good about it.
好吧 希望你会希望被扔得
Okay, well, then I hope you enjoy lots of balls
满脸蛋蛋
in your face.
在火人节我都能安然度过
If I didn't at Burning Man,
在这里我也能行
I doubt I will here.
Gordon 嗨
Gordon, hi.
就像你预测的那样
As you predicted,
我们今天要分开展示我们的品牌
today we'll be presenting our brands separately.
好的 看来今天有一个品牌要被淘汰了 伙计们
Okay, looks like we have us a brand off, folks.
太刺激了
This is exciting.
我都心花怒放了!
I am feeling it!
Ellen 我知道你不太习惯孤单
Ellen, I know you're not used to being alone.
我以前也不习惯 所以有了第三个老婆
Neither was I, hence wife number three.
别着急
Don't rush.
把大家的注意力拉回你自己身上
Take some time to get yourself centered.
哟 哟 哟! 切克闹!
Yo, yo, yo! What's happening, Sheridan!
美女Ellen驾到
Ellen in the house.
热烈掌声响起来
Let me hear some noise.
噢! 好啦 好啦
Yeah. Oh! All right, all right.
这里有几个喷子 但没关系
We got some haters. That's cool.
Ellen 你设计商标了吗?
Ellen, did you design a logo?
当然 给他们看看 放幻灯片的
Sure did. Show it, player.
George 她在跟你说话呢
George, she's talking to you.
噢 视觉效果还不错
Oh, good impact.
砰 一看就知道是买蛋糕的
Boom, cupcake business.
但是...
But, um...
你店铺的名字在哪儿
Where's the name of your business.
姐儿不需要
Oh, I didn't want one.
姐儿就是要这种酷酷的感觉
I just wanted it to be cool.
让我来解释一下
So let me get this correct.
你想用T恤为你的生意宣传
You want to make T-shirts for your business
但T恤和你的生意又没有关联
With no business connection.
好吧
Okay.
这是你的从商之路 但到这可能就结束了
This is your journey, but it might end here.
不 不 不 看见没 上面是纸杯蛋糕
No, no, no, see, it's a cupcake,
我们卖的是纸杯蛋糕 所以这是我们的"伤业"
and we sell cupcakes, so that's the "bidness."
好吧 你猜怎么着? 老娘不干了!
Okay, you know what? Screw this!
那件T恤酷毙了 如果你们体会不到
That t-shirt is way cool, and if you can't see it,
这个培训根本不值我花一千块钱
this seminar is so not worth the $1,000 I paid.
拜拜
Peace out.
在生意圈儿里 我们管这个叫倒闭
In business, we call that a meltdown.
时有发生
It happens.
下面有请Ellen的前合伙人Pam
So why don't we bring up Ellen's former partner Pam.
让我们热烈欢迎Pam
Let's give Pam a round of applause.
Max 我没必要到上面去了
Max, I don't have to go up there.
走吧 我们离开这
Come on, we can just leave.
看看是谁
Oh, look who wants
要卷起铺盖走人了
to pack up their guitar suitcase and go.
你知道吗?
You know what?
我想离开是因为你失败了
I was only leaving 'cause you failed.
我对自己的点子很有信心
I believe in my ideas.
大家下午好
Good afternoon. Hello, hi.
我是 Max自制纸杯蛋糕店的代表
I represent Max's homemade cupcakes.
我要打断你一下
I'm gonna stop you right there.
为什么是Max蛋糕店
Why Max's cupcakes?
为什么不是Ellen或者Pam蛋糕店?
Why not Ellen's or Pam's?
嗯...
Well, um...
Max是... Max是一位很特别的人
Max was... Max is this very special person
是她启发了我们做这个生意
and the inspiration behind our whole business.
明白了
Got it.
所以Max 是你和你生意的
So Max is an emotional touchstone
感情纽带
for you and your business.
是的
Yes.
好理由 继续说
Valid. Go on.
好的
Great.
咱们看看商标...
So the logo...
George 请
George.
这是我们公司目前的商标
This is our current company logo,
我感觉用它挺好的
and I feel it works just fine.
只要它没烂没破 就用不着理了 对吧?
I mean, if it ain't broke, don't fix it, right?
行啦
Okay.
我们的纸杯蛋糕是甜蜜的象征
Well, the cupcake shows a mix of sweet imagery
因为我们两个女孩一直想让
Because we're two girls trying to retro-repurpose the phrase
"香香甜甜 美好无限"这句话再火一把
"sugar and spice and everything nice."
嘿 嘿! 嘿 嘿 嘿 嘿 嘿!
Hey, hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
别扔了!
Leave Pam alone!
我没事 Ellen
I'm fine, Ellen.
他们打不倒我 因为我对我们
They can't shut me down, because I believe in us
以及我们精美的手工纸杯蛋糕有信心
and our special brand of artisan cupcakes.
为什么?
Why?
话筒给我!
Give me!
去死吧 你们这群潘 去死 去死!
Eat it, you losers! Eat it, eat it!
我发现没人朝你们扔真理球了
I see the truth balls have stopped.
看来"去死 去死 潘棵"
It looks like "eat it, eat it, you losers."
可以做你们的品牌
might just be your brand.
你们两个就是一个香甜组合
You two are a combination of sugar and spice
但是世事并不美好
and things not so nice.
说到真相 你们要把培训的钱补交给Sandra
Speaking of truth, I need you to pay Sandra for the seminar.
我十分敬佩你们的勇气
As much as I admire your pluck,
但是你们吃了十二次的意大利面不是免费
12 trips to the pasta bar aren't free.
- 走吧 Pam   - 好的 我们走 Ellen
- Come on, Pam.  - Yeah, let's go, Ellen.
我就是Ellen
I'm Ellen.
猜猜我大衣里面是什么
Guess what I have under my coat.
反正你不会去做缩胸手术
Well, I know it's not a boob reduction.
你觉得怎么样? 很酷 是吧?
What do you think? Cool, huh?
噢 该死的 已经有人做这种T恤了?
Aw, man, somebody already makes that?
太遗憾了
Oh, bummer.
就像以前我以为是自己发明了土豆条三明治
This is like when I thought I invented chip-wiches.
其实早该知道的 我以前都吃过一次了
Should've known. I was eating one at the time.
不 Max 这是你发明的T恤
No, Max, this is your shirt.
我在研讨会上拿到了你的设计
I got the rendering from the seminar
然后把它做了出来
and had it made it
我们在"快又好"可以做任何东西
We can make anything in "Under An Hour."
你知道的 就在你被捕的那座桥下面
You know, that place under the bridge
那间未成年酒吧的旁边
near the underage bar where you got under arrest.
不会吧
No way.
真不敢相信 太性感了
Oh, no way. That's hot.
我知道 那地方还有个女孩子
I know, and a girl at the place
还问我在哪儿能买到呢
asked me where she could get one.
真的吗?
Really?
我都有点儿爱上我自己了
Kind of in love with myself right now.
嘿 是什么让你改变了对那个T恤的看法?
Hey, what made you change your mind about the T-shirts?
我在沃顿商学院学到的一件事就是
Well, one of the things I learned at wharton
成功取决于要听取更好的创意
is that success depends on staying open
即使这创意不是你想出来的
to a better idea, even if it's not yours.
对了 你也有一件
Aw. And here.
我觉得你应该喜欢黑色的
I thought you'd rather a black one.
在约炮软件和生活中都适用
On Tinder and in life.